Time!
时间到!
All right,Klingons, pencils down.
好咧 克林贡小盆友们 停笔
(Klingon 人类发明的外星语言)
Okay,I have "pokh."
好吧 我做出来"Pokh"
- Have it.
- Got it.
- 一样
- 也有
"Potl."
"Potl"
- Yup.
- Have it.
- 没错
- 我也是
"Pukhpa."
"Pukhpa"
- Have it. -
Got it. - Yup.
- 一样
- 也有
I have "chorrr."
我做出来"Chorrr"
- Got it.
- Yup.
- 有
- 对
- "Nekhmakh."
- Yeah.
- "Nekhmakh"
- 没错
And "kreplach."
还有"Kreplach"
- Hold on a second. "Kreplach?"
- Yeah.
- 等会儿 "Kreplach"?
- 是啊
That isn't Klingon; it's
Yiddish for meat-filled dumpling.
这哪是克林贡语 这是依地语 指肉馅饺子
(Yiddish 犹太人使用的国际语)
Well,as it turns out,
it's also a Klingon word.
这样是没错啦 但它也是克林贡语单词噢
Really? Define it.
真的假的? 啥意思来着
"Kreplach": A hearty
Klingon... dumpling.
"Kreplach"意思是丰满的克林贡饺子
- Judge's ruling?
- Bilurrrbe.
- 裁判怎么说?
- Bilurrrbe(不对)
Hey,guys,I need to use your TV.
嘿 小伙子们 我要用下你们的电视机
What's wrong with your TV?
你的电视机咋了?
I don't know. It just died.
I'm getting a bunch of static.
不晓得呢 开出来一片雪花 都是噪音
Did you pay your cable bill?
你交了有线电视费没?
Ugh,you sound just
like the cable company.
呃 你是收有线电视费的咩
All right,so,shh! Tyra Banks is about to
kick someone off America's Next Top Model.
嘘! Tyra Banks要踢掉一个美国超模了
- Excuse me,Penny, but we're...
- No,no,don't tell her.
- 抱歉 Penny 我们在...
- 别告诉她
playing Klingon Boggle.
玩克林贡语拼词游戏
What do you mean,"Aw"? Like
she didn't know we were nerds?
你"嗷"是啥意思?
好像她不知道我们是群呆子一样
All right,if you must watch, then
mute it with closed captions,please.
好吧 如果你非看不可
就开静音看字幕好了噢
Fine.
成
All right,Boggle warriors... kapla'!
好咧 拼词小将们 Kapla!(开始啦)
Look at those women.
瞧瞧那些女人
They're gorgeous.
真漂亮
"Worf," nice! Too bad
that's a proper noun.
"Worf" 赞! 可惜那是个专有名词
Oh,look,there's the
future Mrs. Wolowitz.
噢 瞧啊 那不是未来的Wolowitz太太嘛
No,wait,that'sthe future Mrs. Wolowitz.
不 等会儿 那才是未来的Wolowitz太太
With her head in the lap
of... Oh,what a coincidence.
她的头正巧... 噢 哪有这么巧
It's the future Mrs. Wolowitz.
这就是未来的Wolowitz太太
Yeah,and they can all move
in with you and your mother.
没错 她们都能搬来同你和你妈一起住
The current Mrs. Wolowitz.
现任Wolowitz太太
Is "qochbe'" spelled with a
(gargling) or a (guttural grunt)?
"Qochbe"怎么拼来着? 咳嗽音还是咕哝音?
Why is that Mrs. Wolowitz crying?
那个Wolowitz太太为啥哭了?
That's Anais. None of the other
girls in the house like her.
那个是Anais 那屋子没人喜欢她
House? What house?
屋子? 啥屋子?
They all live in a house together.
她们同居一处屋檐下啊
A house,where?
哪儿哪儿?
I don't know. Somewhere in L.A.
我不知道呢 洛杉矶某处吧
Wait a minute.
等等
You're telling me that I'm within driving distance
of a house filled with aspiring supermodels?
你是说我距一幢满是
热辣超模的屋子仅仅几步之遥?
Yeah,I guess.
没错 我猜是这样
And they live together
and shower together and...
而且她们同住还同浴还...
have naked pillow fights?
赤果果滴用枕头打闹?
Hey,wh-where are you going?
嘿 你上哪儿去?
To pay my cable bill.
还是去交有线电视费吧
All right,pencils down!
好咯 停笔!
I have "lokh," "makh," and
"cherrrkh. " Anybody got those?
我做出来"Lokh" "Makh" "Cherrrkh"
你们做出来没?
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧http://sfile.ydy.com=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:咔肉肉
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 饭特稀 王泳东 老辣菜
校对: penny
时间轴: 咔肉肉
双语:徐小帆
The Big Bang
Theory Season02 Episode07
天才理论传
第二季 第7集
Did I miss anything? Did
they kick Giselle off?
我错过啥好戏没? Giselle有没被淘汰?
Not yet, but her underwater
photo shoot was an embarrassment.
还没 可她的水下照可真
Sadly,Mrs. Giselle Wolowitz
is sensitive to chlorine.
真桑心啊 Giselle Wolowitz太太对氯过敏
Lucky for her I like my fashion
models pruny and bug-eyed.
她还真走运 我就喜欢傻傻的暴眼模特
Sheldon,the food's here.
Sheldon 吃的买来了
Ooh,there's the house.
Freeze frame, freeze frame.
噢 就是这栋房子 定格 定格
What are you doing?
你干嘛呢?
Marking the star positions and physical landmarks
so we can find the house of the supermodels.
把星星的位置和地标拓下来
这样我们就能找到超模之家了
Why?
找那干啥?
Isn't it obvious?Every week,they
kick out a beautiful girl,
不明摆这嘛 每周都有个漂亮姑娘被淘汰
making her feel unwanted
and without self-esteem.
使她感到被人嫌弃 无地自容
A.k.a. the future Mrs. Howard Wolowitz.
她就是...Howard Wolowitz他未来太太
- Is my hamburger medium well?
- Yes.
- 汉堡五分熟?
- 是的
- Dill slices,not sweet?
- Yes.
- 加了不甜的莳萝片?
- 是的
- Individual relish packets?
- Yes.
- 独立调味包?
- 是的
- Onion rings?
- Yes.
- 放了洋葱圈?
- 是的
- Extra breading?
- I asked.
- 多加一块面包没?
- 我问了
- What did they say?
- No.
- 他们怎么说?
- 没门
- Did you protest?
- Yes.
- 你抗议没?
- 当然
- Vociferously?
- No.
- 大声嚷嚷着?
- 没有
Well,then what took you so long?
那咋还那么久咧?
Just eat.
吃你的吧
Hey,guys,what'd I miss? What'd I miss?
嘿 小伙子们 我错过啥没? 我错过啥没?
Giselle's hanging by a thread.
Giselle命悬一线
Oh,good,I hate her.
噢 真棒 我讨厌她
Then you're not invited to our wedding.
那你可参加不了我们婚礼了
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- 这是你的
- 多谢
Oh,do we have to suffer through this
transparently manipulative pseudo-reality again?
噢 我们又要忍受这
这明显人为操纵的伪真人秀?
Yes.
是啊
You and I have a standing TV schedule, which is
the result of extensive debate and compromise.
我们有份固定电视节目表的
那可是咱论战和妥协的产物啊
Any alterations except for breaking news have to
be pre-approved at the weekly roommate meeting.
除爆炸新闻外的一切变更
需提前经由每周室友会议批准
Put it on the agenda.
那提上议事日程吧
genda.
提上议事日程前你得提出动议啊
Oh,I'll make a motion, but
you're not going to like it.
好 我会提出动议的 可你不会喜欢的
Fine. Mock Parliamentary procedure.
好呀 还藐视议会程序
At least put it on mute.
至少开静音吧
Oh,Giselle's not getting kicked
off. It's totally going to be Summer.
噢 Giselle淘汰不掉了 肯定是Summer了
What?
咋了?
Sheldon's onion ring. Just put it back!
Sheldon的洋葱圈 快放回去!
- It's one onion ring.
- Just put it back before he comes!
- 不过是个洋葱圈
- 趁他还没回来 快放回去!
No,no,no! No,I don't
think that's where it was.
不不不! 好像不是那位置吧
Okay,here he comes.
Deny,deny,people. Wall of silence.
好吧 他回来了 抵赖 抵赖哦
全部装木头人
- Who touched my...
- Penny! Penny did it.
- 谁碰了我的...
- Penny! 是Penny干的...
Why would you do that?
你为何要这样做?
I don't know. I was
hungry? What's the big deal?
不知道啊 我饿了? 有啥要紧的么?
The big deal is that nobody
touches food on my plate.
要紧的是没人能碰我盘子里的食物
All right. Look, I
didn't know,I'm sorry.
好吧 听着 不知者无罪 对不起
Well,I'm sorry,but that
is your second strike.
得 我很抱歉 但你已经二振了
What?
啥?
You have two strikes.
你已经二振了
Three strikes and you're out.
三振就出局了
It's a sports metaphor.
体育比喻呗
- A sports metaphor?
- Yes,baseball.
- 体育比喻?
- 对呀 垒球知道不
All right,yeah. I-I'll play
along. What was my first strike?
好 就算这么说 我何时被一振的?
March 18th. You violated my rule
about forwarding email humor.
3月18日 你坏了我发电邮幽默的规矩
I did?
有吗?
The photo of the cat who
wants to "has cheezeburger"?
想"乞"芝士汉堡的猫的图片?
Oh,come on. Everybody loves "LOL cats."
不是吧 大家都喜欢"欢乐猫"
They're cute and they can't
spell 'cause they're cats.
可爱 写字又写不对 因为是猫猫嘛
I trusted you with my email address, and you betrayed
that trust by sending me Internet banality: strike one.
我信任你 才给你邮箱地址
你却给我发些网络俗物:一振
Touching my food: strike two.
碰我的吃的:二振
Don't worry. They only stay
on your record for a year.
没事的 污点只会记录一年的
You can get them removed early,
but you have to take his class.
你也可以提前解禁 但得听他的训导
Come on,I touched one onion ring.
不是吧 我只碰了一个洋葱圈
Yeah,and then you put it back, compromising
the integrity of all the other onion rings.
但你又放回去了
危害到其余所有洋葱圈
Oh,honey,the buses don't
go where you live,do they?
小可怜 你住的地方公交都不敢路过 对吧?
Look,Penny,I wish I could
be more lenient with you,
Penny 我也想对你慈悲为怀
but since you've become a permanent
member of our social group,
但既然你要在我社交圈常驻
I have to hold you to the same
standards as everybody else.
我必须对你一视同仁了
Congratulations. You're
officially one of us.
恭喜正式入伙
One of us,one of us.
入伙万岁 入伙万岁
Well,what a thrill.
多振奋人呀
You're sitting in my spot.
你坐我位置上了
Oh,jeez,you've got to be kidding me.
天呀 你不是吧
Leonard,she's in my spot.
Leonard 她占人家位置啦
Yeah,yeah. Uh,see, here's the thing.
嗯 嗯 事实上
After you leave,I still
have to live with him.
你走了 我还得和他一起过日子呢
I don't care. I'm taking
a stand. Metaphorically.
管我鸟事 我坚定立场
比喻哦 不是真立起来
All right,that's it. Strike three.
别怪我无情 三振出局了你
Ooh,strike three.
怕怕的三振
I'm banished? What the
hell kind of crap is that?
驱逐我? 哪门子鬼话?
Listen,don't worry. I'll talk to him.
没事的 我会和他谈谈的
Yeah,you do that.
最好那样
Just so I know,would you
be open to taking his class?
我想知道 你有可能听他训导吗?
You can do it online!
网上也成呀!
So based on our triangulation, we've narrowed down the location
of theTop Modelhouse to three square miles in the Hollywood Hills.
根据三角测量 超模之家搜索范围
已缩小到好莱坞山的3平方英里
Or possibly Durham,Noh Carolina.
也可能是北卡洲的达勒姆
When we find it, you want to go with us?
要是找到了 和我们去吗?
To do what?
去干什么?
Party with the pretty girls, dude!
和美女们狂欢呀 老兄!
Are you insane?
脑子进水了吧?
You're not going to party with them.
还跟她们狂欢呢
You're not even going to
get anywhere near that place.
你们都不能靠近那里
That's what they said to
Neil Armstrong about the moon.
阿姆斯特朗登月前 人们也这么说
No one said anything of
the kind to Neil Armstrong.
根本没人说阿姆斯特朗什么
The entire nation dedicated a decade of
effort and treasure to put a man on the moon.
全国用进十年的努力和资金
将他送上月球的
Well,my fellow Americans, before this year is out,
we will put a Wolowitz on one of America's top models.
我的美国朋友们 今年之内
我们将送Wolowitz登陆美国超模
And a large number of people
will believe it never happened.
大多数人都会觉得你白日梦
Okay,let me guess.
我看看
A quesadilla with soy cheese for
the lactose-intolerant Leonard.
不爱乳糖的Leonard要豆奶干酪玉米饼
Thank you.
谢谢
Shrimp Caesar salad with no almonds for the highly
allergic kosher-only-on-the-high-holidays Howard.
只在犹太大节吃合食的Howard
因为过敏 要不加杏仁的恺撒沙拉虾
And for our suddenly "back on the Hindu
wagon" Raj, the meatlover's pizza, no meat.
突然回归印度风俗的Raj
至尊肉披萨 不含肉
Coming right up.
马上来
Wait. Excuse me.
等下
You forgot my barbecue bacon cheeseburger,
barbecue sauce, bacon and cheese on the side.
你忘了我的 照烧培根芝士汉堡
烧烤酱 熏肉 芝士要放边上
Oh,I didn't tell you?
没告诉你吗?
You're banished from
the Cheesecake Factory.
你被我们店驱除了
Why?
凭啥?
Well,you have three strikes.
你被三振出局了
One: coming in. Two: sitting down.
And three: I don't like your attitude.
第一次: 进来 第二次: 坐下
第三次: 烦死你的态度了
You can't do that.
你无权这么干
Not only is it a violation of California state law, it
flies directly in the face of Cheesecake Factory policy.
不仅触犯了加州法律
还极大的违反了你们的店规
Yeah,no,there's a new policy:
No shoes,no shirt, no Sheldon.
不 新规定--衣冠不整者和Sheldon不得入内
I bet we could sell that
sign all over Pasadena.
我打赌这标语在帕萨迪纳各处
都能买个好价钱
Penny,can I talk to you for a minute?
Penny可以过来谈下吗?
Well,here's the thing.
是这样的
Um,I talked to Sheldon and he
feels terrible and he agrees
我和Sheldon谈过了 他也不好受
that he was unreasonable
and out of line.
他也觉得自己无理取闹 有些过分了
Really? Well, that's great.
真的?很好呀
Yeah,so just apologize to him,okay?
就给他道个小歉嘛?
What? I'm not going to
apologize to that nutcase.
啥?老娘才不给那疯子道歉呢
Oh,come on. It's easy. He'll
even tell you what to say.
别呀 很简单的
他甚至会指导你该咋说的
Leonard,don't you get it?
Leonard 你不明白吗?
If you guys keep going along with his
insanity, you're just encouraging him.
如果你们老对他的无理让步
会助长他的嚣张
We're not encouraging. It's
more like... knuckling under.
不是纵容呀 更像是...屈服淫威
Look,I like hanging out with you guys, but I'm
not going to apologize for something I didn't do.
我很喜欢和你们玩
但我不会为莫须有的罪名道歉
Well,actually,technically,
you did do it.
其实 理论上说 你干过的
That's strike one,Leonard.
一振警告你 Leonard
There you go: quesadilla.
Salad. There's your pizza.
来了 玉米饼 沙拉 还有披萨
And thanks to Sheldon's heated discussion with
my manager one barbecue bacon cheeseburger,
Sheldon和经理激昂争辩换来的
照烧培根芝士汉堡
barbecue sauce,bacon
and cheese on the side.
烧烤酱 熏肉 芝士 放边上了
Thank you.
谢谢你
Go ahead. Eat it.
试试看 吃呀
I dare you.
看你敢不
That's it. There's the house.
I foundAmerica's top models!
找到了 就这房子 我找到全美超模了!
Are you sure?
确定吗?
Look,on the roof. Anais
and Giselle are sunbathing.
看屋顶 Anais和Giselle在日光浴
European-style.
欧式的
You can recognize
people on Google Earth?
你能在谷歌地球上认出人来?
Of course not. I got a buddy of mine
at NORAD to have a spy drone fly over.
肯定不行的 我让北美防空司令部一哥们
开无人驾驶飞机拍的呗
NORAD? You're using military aircraft?
防空司令部? 你在用国防航行器?
It was already targeted to poke
around a nuclear reactor in Siberia.
已经设定搜寻西伯利亚的核反应堆了
I took it an hour out of its way,tops.
我最多半路借用一个小时
Okay,where is he?
他在哪儿?
Sheldon? I just dropped him off
at the comic book store. Why?
Sheldon? 我刚把他送到漫画书店了 干嘛?
Here. Try and go online.
试试看 上网
- Problem with the WiFi?
- Just try.
- 无线网坏了?
- 试下就知道
Greetings,hamburger toucher.
你好 汉堡亵渎者
You are probably wondering why you
cannot IM with your little friends about
可能你很纳闷咋不能和
你的密友们网聊了呢
how much you "heart" various things.
无法倾诉你多么"心水"啥啥啥了
This recorded message is alerting you that I am putting
an end to your parasitic piggybacking upon our WiFi.
这段信息是通告你
蹭我们网上的日子结束了
If you want to remedy the situation,
you can contact the phone company,
如果你想补救的话
可以给电话公司联系下
set up your own WiFi and pay for
it,or you may apologize to me.
自己花钱安无线网络
或者呢 向我道歉哦
Well?
如何?
I reiterate: knuckle under.
还是那句 屈服吧
No,no,no,no,no. It is on. I am gonna
introduce your friend to a world of hurt.
不 不 不 不 我卯上了
我要让他见识下悲惨世界
Oh,Penny,you don't want to
get into it with Sheldon.
Penny 别和Sheldon过不去
The guy is one lab accident
away from being a supervillain.
这家伙可是出个啥实验室意外
就会变成超级恶人的苗子
I don't care. I was in junior rodeo.
老娘不管 我参加过初级牛仔竞技
I can hogtie and castrate
him in 60 seconds.
一分钟以内 我就可以捆它四肢 阉割完毕
No need to neuter the nerd.
I can get you back online.
不需要把那书呆子变太监
我能让你上上网
There,see? Problem solved.
瞧? 问题解决了
Voil.
搞定
Hello,puny insects.
好哇 卑鄙小人们
As a consequence of your efforts to circumvent my
will, everyone is awarded one additional strike.
作为违背我意愿的惩罚
每人额外奖励一振
Thanks a lot,Howard.
真是多谢你了 Howard
What are you complaining about? I'm
the one who has to take the class again.
你抱怨个屁? 我可是又要上课听训的说
Hello.
你好
Time to do your laundry,huh?
洗衣时间 啊哈?
It's Saturday night.
今天是星期六
Saturday is laundry night.
周六晚是洗衣时间
I know.
我知道
Every Saturday at 8:15.
每个周六晚上8:15
Easy to anticipate.
地球人都知道
What are you implying?
你在暗示什么?
I'm implying that you're
a creature of habit.
我暗示你是个习惯性动物
And if something were to prevent you from
doing your laundry on Saturday at 8:15,
如果有状况阻止你在周六晚的8:15洗衣服
you might find it...unpleasant.
你会...不开心哟
Knuckle under? My ass.
看谁屈服
Oh,no,are all the machines taken?
噢 不 所有的洗衣机都满了?
What are you gonna do?
你该怎么办呢?
No problem.
没关系
I'll just do my laundry another night.
我改天晚上再洗
Another night? Well,I guess you
can try, but deep inside your heart,
改天晚上? 你嘴上这么说 但内心深处
you'll know that laundry
night is always Saturday night.
你知道周六晚上才是洗衣时间
Woman,you are playing with
forces beyond your ken.
小妹妹 你这点小伎俩可别玩过火了
Yeah,well,your ken can kiss my Barbie.
是吗 你伎俩高明来拍我马屁呀
Sheldon. Sheldon! Sheldon.
Sheldon Sheldon! Sheldon!
Yes?
咋了?
Where are my clothes?
我的衣服在哪里?
Your clothes?
你的衣服?
Yes,I left them in the washers and when
I went down to get them,they were gone.
是的 我留在洗衣机里的
我再下去拿时 它们不见了
Really?
真的?
Despite the sign that says "Do
not leave laundry unattended"?
你难道没看警告 "别让衣物离开你的视线"?
Sheldon,where are my clothes?
Sheldon 我的衣服在哪里?
You know,I do recall seeing some
female undergarments. Where was that?
知道吗 我好像看到过一些
女人的内衣哟 在哪里呢?
Oh,yes... Earlier this evening, I happened to
gaze out the window and a brassiere caught my eye.
噢 有了...今晚早些时候
我无意往窗外看 一个胸罩映入我眼帘
Do those look familiar?
那些看起来眼熟吗?
How the hell did you get them
up on that telephone wire?
你他妈怎么把它们弄到电话线上去的?
When you understand the laws of
physics,Penny, anything is possible.
当你懂得物理原理的时候 Penny
一切皆有可能
And may I add:
mwuh-ha-ha.
请容我加一句 哇-哈-哈
- Get them down.
- Apologize.
- 把他们弄下来
- 先道歉
Never.
休想
Well,then may I suggest you get a
very long stick and play panty pi帽ata.
那么我建议你找根竹竿 慢慢挑吧
Look,wait,Sheldon,this has
gotten out of hand,okay?
听着 等等 Sheldon 这是太离谱了 好吗?
I've done some stupid things.
我做了些傻事
You've done some stupid things.
你也做了些傻事
How about we just call it even
and move on with our lives?
我们算扯平了 就此收手
继续过日子怎么样?
I've done no stupid things.
我才没有干傻事呢
Look,you've got to meet me halfway here.
听着 你多少得让点步吧
I am meeting you halfway.
我已经让步了
I'm willing to concede that
you've done stupid things.
我都愿意承认你干了傻事了
Hey,you guys are talking again. Good.
嘿 你们又说话了 很好哇
What happened?
发生了什么事?
Leonard,rember when I said it was
on? Well,now it's junior rodeo on.
Leonard 还记得我说过要开战吗?
好吧 现在是阉牛时间
Oh,not junior rodeo.
噢 表这样子啦
What did you do?
你干了什么?
I had no choice, Leonard.
我没的选 Leonard
She ruined laundry night.
她破坏了洗衣之夜
Telephone wires can't
electrocute you,can they?
电话线不会电人的吧?
No. Look,this has to stop.
不会 听着 不能再荒唐下去了
Oh,no,no,no. It is just beginning.
噢 不 不 不 好戏才刚开始呢
All right,I really didn't
want to do this,but... here.
好吧 我真的不想这么干 但是...给你
What's this?
这是什么?
Sheldon's Kryptonite.
Sheldon的死穴
Oh,my God.
噢 天哪
He can never know that
I gave that to you.
死都不能让他知道是我给你的
Look,I said I wanted to
hurt him,but... but this?
听着 我说过要给他点颜色看 但...但这个?
It'll shorten the war by five
years and save millions of lives.
这能缩短5年的战争 还能拯救数百万苍生
Oh,pause it. That's it. Confirmed.
噢 暂停 就是它 对头
We now have the address
of theTop Modelhouse.
我们找到了超模之家的地址
God bless you,Google Street
View registered trademark.
上帝保佑你吧 谷歌街景
Okay,for the record, what
you're doing is really creepy.
好吧 说真的 你们让人心里发毛
You know what? If it's "creepy" to
use the Internet, military satellites,
如果"心里发毛"是指用网络 军用卫星
and robot aircraft to find a
house full of gorgeous young models
和无人驾驶飞机
找到装满美貌年轻的模特的房子
so that I can drop in on them
unexpectedly, then fine,I'm "creepy."
然后让我来个意外到访的话
那好吧 我是让人"心里发毛"
Hello. Yeah,hold on a
second. I'll get him.
喂 好的 等等 我叫他来接
Sheldon,it's for you.
Sheldon 你的电话
- Who is it?
- Your mother.
- 谁打来的?
- 你老妈
Oh,good.
噢 很好
Hi,Mom. How are you?
嗨 妈妈 你好吗?
But,Mom... she keeps sitting in my spot.
但是 妈妈...她总坐人家位子嘛
And-and she touched my food.
还有-还有她碰了我的食物
Okay,yes,I took her clothes,
but she started it...
好吧 是的 我拿了她的衣服
但是她先开火的...
No,that's not fair.
不 这不公平
Why should I have to apologize?
为什么要我去道歉?
Yeah,I really don't think this is the
kind of thing Jesus concerns himself with.
我不认为耶稣会管这等闲事
No,you're right. I don't really
know what Jesus thinks about.
不 你说的对 我真的不知道耶稣在想什么
All right,good-bye.
好吧 再见
Did you tell on me?
是你告的密?
Are you kidding me? I
already have two strikes.
开什么玩笑? 我都已经二振了
Penny. Penny. Penny.
Penny Penny Penny
I am very,very sorry
for what I have done.
非常非常抱歉 为我的行为道歉
Here's your laundry.
这是你的衣服
I rescind your strikes and
you are no longer banished.
我废除了你的记录 你不再被驱逐了
Can I sit wherever I want?
我想坐哪就坐哪了不?
Never mind,never mind.
That's,that's not important.
没事 没事 这个--这个不重要
Sheldon,this was big of you.
Thank you. I really appreciate it.
Sheldon 你真的很宽宏大量
谢谢你 我很感激
Thank you.
谢谢
- Good night,Sheldon.
- Penny...
- 晚安 Sheldon
- Yes?
- Well played.
- 啥?
- 你有一手
Thank you.
谢谢
Just rember: with great power
comes great responsibility.
但请记住 能力越大 责任越大
(出自)
Understood.
明白
Can I help you?
有什么事吗?
Yes,we're here to fix the cable.
我们是来修有线电视的
I think we have satellite.
我想我们装的是卫星的
That's what I meant.
我说的就是卫星
Okay,come on in.
好吧 请进
She's taller than all the
women in my family combined.
她比我家里女人摞一起都高
What do we do now?
我们接下来干什么?
Follow Mrs. Wolowitz.
跟着Wolowitz太太走呗
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
天才理论传
第二季 第7集 完